How to tie your legs
Legs...
What is how to tie your legs?
Don't you know
how to tie this board?
It's...
You don't know how to tie this line, right?
This
board
It's...
For example, this model
This model
Because you have a
basicocentrometer
Let me show you
There are several
The first one is the basicocentrometer
It's a circle
Another one is
the surface circumference
I will tell you the difference
The surface circumference is the one that sticks to the body
So it will go in
The basic circumference
There is no way to stick it to the body, it will directly select the most prominent point in the middle and connect it to the line.
Generally speaking, this dress will not stick to the body, but sometimes it is more special.
For example, like that kind of coat, it will stick to your body.
In fact, it's hard to say.
Sometimes, in a special situation, you want it to stick to the body and connect to the line.
Then there is the basic length measurement.
In the basic length measurement, why don't I use the circle measurement?
Because it is a whole circle.
If we use the circle measurement, it is created like this.
There is no way to stick it.
So we use the basic length measurement.
Set two positions for it.
Assume that you set two positions like this.
After setting two positions, the length measurement is one-stop.
Then if you stick the long board to it for a whole section.
For example, stick it to the virtual model measurement.
It will stick to it for a whole section.
Then this section will...
You see it just flew away.
It is easy to be unstable.
So I will cut out a section in the middle.
Then stick the section cut in the middle to it.
In this way, there is no way for it to move back and forth.
It is fixed here.
At most, it is a horizontal movement like this.
We just made a circle.
If you fix it on both sides, it won't move.
Then there is the arm here, the wrist here.
For example, the sleeve.
Shoe cuff.
You have to lock it in the wrist position.
Then we will make a board for it like this.
Then stick it here.
After sticking it here, I will simulate it.
It is a circle.
See?
It will be stuck here and won't move.
It won't be affected by the force of gravity.
For example, like this.
Let's change the movement for it.
Modulate and change at the same time.
It moves too fast.
Sometimes, for example, your hand...
Oops, it moves too fast.
Forget it.
It doesn't matter.
Sometimes, when your arm is bent,
the sleeve will fall down.
Then it will be stuck here and won't fall.
Then, because we used the TFT model measurement,
what other useful things does it have?
For example, some people want to do the floating effect of the sleeve.
What is the floating effect of the sleeve?
There are some 2D cartoons.
Their sleeves are big.
But the sleeves won't fall down.
There is still a lantern sleeve stuck here.
Under normal circumstances,
lantern sleeves,
the sleeve will fall to the wrist.
But some 2D cartoons,
the sleeve is so big that it won't fall down.
You can use this tool to lock it here.
Then it has a conflict thickness.
Increase the conflict thickness a little bit.
It is a floating effect.
See?
Increase it a little bit.
It is like this.
There is a ring on the arm.
Just like this.
See?
Have you learned it?
Let me see.
Let's see what it says.
Use 1.
Change the action.
The TFT model is not compatible.
Then the TFT model is not compatible.
Your face is different.
TFT model.
Both TFT models need to be in the form of OBJ.
Into Marvelous Designer.
How to fix the wrist is not clear.
This is some people.
It just needs to be very stiff.
If the effect,
you can make it floating.
Then I use this TFT model to fix it.
Then paste it to the circumference measurement
This is pasted to it
Then it will be pasted to this area
Then the gap in the middle
We do it with conflict thickness
Conflict thickness
See no
then
After doing it, give it a shape optimization
Then delete the measurement
Like this
It will be shaped
At this time
You can still
Drag and move this plate
You can still let it
You can make some changes
You can make some slight adjustments
For example
I don't know
Anyway, you can move it
At this time
Conflict thickness
it will also be that, that is, it has this, this conflict thickness, or, or a ring here,
and then just say you have that, uh, have that fixed, this measurement, then it will not fall down this sleeve,
in doing some action when, that is, it can do counter gravity,
this can only be, uh, it can not be said that it can only be positive and negative,
because it adds that air thickness, that is, the conflict thickness, it is a circle of air thickness around the plate,
and then it is because it is a circle along this plate, so it, in general, your hand, your hand is round,
it is with your hand, your hand is what shape, it will follow what shape to come,
uh,
this is also a very small part, that is, sometimes it just has to do that kind of counter gravity effect,
it can only be used in this way,
if it stipulates what this thing is, what shape it is, then you just make it a support inside,
like the kind of water embroidery I did before,
what about the water embroidery, it will expand into a horn shape here,
and then this is also fine, this is also a poured over,
uh,
then you may have to do it in the middle, make it a, this is thin,
this is a support for chasing,
ah,
anyway, this is, um,
this is a special time,
this is the thing, it is floating,
it will be used,
this is, uh,
uh,
your name is so funny, that Wang Shengtang,
I just saw that this is Marvelous Designer 12,
the virtual model does not know what to press to become transparent, you press Shift X,
this,
is to open Google, and then you are OBJ,
OBJ, then it does not bring Google, it looks transparent,
how
can I do this?
this one is just like a
when you're afraid,
it will make a YouTube video out of it,
these people want to run this app,
if you want this one,
there is not just a link,
It's not very clear, this, this thing, this Mooney basic figure is an FBX, he fell into it, and then I called him a virtual model.
You know,
it's, it's, whether it's OBJ or FBX, you can import it into the format of a virtual model. It's just a way of saying it.
We call him virtual model in Marvelous Designer.
puerta
Uh, that's about it for today. If you have any other questions, you can come to our QQ group.
What?
Which?
If you want the whole tutorial, please follow our Bilibili account, mdguanfang, and then you can watch our live broadcast.
Ding ding ding ding ding
Ding ding ding
Ding ding
Biliböl
The modern way is this one, the ancient way is another one, or do you want to look at the ancient way?
FBX has an arrangement point, now if you import it as a virtual model, it should automatically generate an arrangement point.
If not, you just use OBJ, if you are using the previous version, you just import FBX into it, and then export it as OBJ, and then import it in, and then select the automatic generation arrangement point.
Can information be sent via file?
It has loop representation!
It shouldn't have any new files?
Thank you for giving your questions!
Thank you for your support to our software!
If there are any questions you would like to ask, please send them into the Qandu Facebook chat!
Thank you!
How to make clothes, props, special sofa, furniture, etc.
If you are interested, you can take a look at our previous tutorials.
If you think the previous tutorials are not enough,
and you want to know more interesting content,
you can send a private message to our account or add our QQ group.
The live broadcast will be posted next week.
Because I only have time to edit videos when I go to work.
So it will definitely wait until next week.
Folding umbrella. Oh, I haven't done a folding umbrella.
I've only done a long ice umbrella. You can take a look.
I don't think it's easy to do a folding umbrella.
But I want to do it.
The folding umbrella in the video is...
The folding umbrella is a long ice umbrella plus a key animation.
Why do we have to use our software to make a folding umbrella?
No, why?
Don't you want it?
Oh, modern.
What is the case of modern clothes?
Are you talking about the other one?
You mean this one?
Oh, this is the ancient one.
This is the other one.
The one I demonstrated at the beginning is the traditional ancient Greek one.
It's made of one piece.
You see, the whole project file may be confused when it is opened.
Why are there only three half pieces?
Oh, the folding umbrella.
You say this.
There is a friend in the group today.
It's about 10 minutes before the live broadcast.
I made a folding umbrella.
He said he wanted to make a folding umbrella.
Then I want to show you.
This is a normal folding umbrella.
How do we girls make a relatively wide folding umbrella?
Then we can see it in Bilibili.
You can see it in Bilibili.
It is published in Bilibili.
This one,
This version is changed with a T-shirt.
And the T-shirt is like this.
Girls wear boys' clothes.
The shoulder line must be moved outward, so you have to move the shoulder line outward.
Then when the shoulder line moves outward, the point of the sleeve, you see, the shoulder line is here, it goes down, right?
Does the point of the sleeve have to follow it down? The point of the sleeve has to move downward.
The sleeve will become a relatively flat sleeve like this from a protruding sleeve.
Other than that, there is nothing else. Other than that, it is also very simple to make a lantern sleeve.
Lantern sleeve is just a little bit, the bottom is a little bit wider than the top, or as long as it is not tightened, it can basically do this effect.
MD can't do fluid simulation.
Don't challenge the limit, we can't try that.
Can't solve the problem.
What is the principle of lantern sleeve? How to change it?
The principle of lantern sleeve is that you take a long side and sew a short side.
Then it was originally a, it was originally sewn together on both sides.
Then it became a lantern sleeve.
The plant body can't be made like that.
Oh, you mean the sleeve?
The sleeve has nothing to do with whether it is a lantern sleeve or not.
What kind of sleeve is it originally?
Oh, you mean here?
Oh, in this case, I will talk about the point when you usually make sleeves.
In fact, look at the front of me.
OK, look at the back of me.
This is not right.
It's just a sleeve.
It only has a curve.
There is never a protruding curve.
See?
If you look at it like this, it is now a curve, right?
There is a little protrusion here.
Just fix it.
Fix the point where you protrude yourself.
This is the setting.
Then this kind of fast to the seam position.
Keep this corner close to 90 degrees.
As close as possible.
Not completely close to 90 degrees.
Then, because you shoulder the line outwards.
You shoulder the line outwards.
Then after you add this chest width.
It will become narrower here.
You try to make this curve.
Don't bend it too much.
Just let it come over like this.
Then this is also coming over.
You don't want to.
You just want to.
Because the curve will become flat after the line is out.
Will become flat.
Then you sew a sleeve like this.
It doesn't seem to be appropriate.
Right?
So just make it a little flat.
Change the sleeve.
I don't know how to change the sleeve.
Go to see that suit.
Or the lesson in the suit.
The lesson in the suit.
I've talked about it.
That is to say.
You change the sleeve.
I don't know how to change it.
You make a big sound first.
After making a big sound.
Freeze your big sound.
Then activate the sleeve.
Don't use the curve of the sleeve in the case of simulation.
To the curve of the sleeve.
The lesson in the suit should be.
How do you do it on the shoulder of the bubble skirt and the bubble sleeve?
That is to turn it over.
It's too loose.
It must be too much fabric to loosen.
So you turn it over like this.
Spread it out like this.
It has more fabric.
When sewing.
This sewing line.
Change it for you.
It has more fabric.
Of course, if you have a bubble sleeve.
You may have a very short sleeve.
And your sleeve is normal.
It won't be like me.
It's like a jacket.
Can AMD make shoes?
It can be bent.
Not hard.
Then you can do it with fabric.
You can do it.
Yes.
Handle and curve point.
I use a lot of curves.
I use it to curve the handle.
Thank you for your support.
You can't sew two big sleeves together.
Can you do it with MD if you don't have roses?
I don't think it's easy to do.
Because that one has to be folded all the time.
Fold all the time.
I think you have to look at it.
I don't know what kind of fabric rose you're talking about.
If it's just a rose.
It's better to sew it up.
But if it's the kind of thing.
It's the kind of thing that's folded with paper.
I don't think it's easy to do.
Okay.
That's about it for today.
We can look forward to seeing you next time.
If you have any other questions.
You can pay attention to our BB account.
MD official.
OK.
I can't make a hole.
I can't make a hole for the time being.
If it's a hole.
You can only dig a hole with the inside line.
But it's still based on the material.
OK.
Thank you for your support.
If you have any other questions.
You can pay attention to our BB account.
MD official.
Or add our.
QQ group.
When I usually go to work.
I have time to be in the group.
To give you technical support and answers.
Thank you for your support all the time.
See you next time.
See you in the next teaching video.
Bye bye.
If you have any questions.
Pay attention to our BB account.
You can check your private message.
There will be a private message.
Bye bye.